♪ We
♪ Are the Crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven: ♪ And if you think we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl
And Steven!
橄榄石!青金石!我到啦!
Peridot! Lapis! I'm here!
你们是不是忘了亲亲史蒂文
Did you forget your favorite Steven
今天要在这儿过夜啊?
was coming over to spend the night?
啊哈!
Aha!
用来敲门的东西
A door-knocky thing!
呃!
Unh!
嘿，以前没见过这个
Hey, that looks new.
橄榄石!青金石!
Peridot! Lapis!
很抱歉我把你们门上的东西弄坏了!
I'm sorry I broke your door thingy!
我想修好来着，但是我不造怎么组装的
I wanted to fix it, but I don't know how it goes together.
用来当面具倒是很不错
Makes a pretty neat mask, though.
哇!
Wow!
我是不是死进了麦片广告里?
Did I just die and go to the back of a cereal box?
啊!啊!
Ah! Aaaah!
嗨，史蒂文
Hi, Steven.
史蒂文!
Steven!
你看我在拖拉机上!
I'm on a tractor!
我是不是不小心溅到你了?
Did I spray you by accident?
一点点而已
Just a little.
你能来真是太棒了
So glad you could make it.
史蒂文!
Steven!
你觉得我们的--
How do you like our little --
实验怎么样?
Experiment?!
不能再棒!
It's amazing.
你们为什么突然之间开始
What made you wanna start farming stuff,
种粮食了?
all of a sudden?
我有培育宝石人
I have all the skills required
所需的技术
for growing Gems.
我就想，为什么不培育些别的呢?
I figured, why not try growing something else?
谁造呢?
Who knows?
说不定他们已经成熟了
Maybe they're ready right now.
你好啊，玉米棒子
Hello, corn.
可能她包在里面听不到吧
Maybe she can't hear me in there.
我照我的形象创造了你!
I made you in my image!
你要听从我的吩咐!
You will do as I say!
等下，你该不会以为
Wait. You didn't think the corn
玉米会自己走起来
was gonna walk right out of the ground
然后听你吩咐对吧?
when you told it to, did you?
蔬菜可不是这样的
That's not how vegetables work.
不是吗?
It's not?
那玉米又有什么意义?!
Well, then, what's the point of corn?!
我得承认，我已经开始怀念
I have to admit, I've really been starting
那些成熟的宝石战士在身边走来走去了
to miss the pitter-patter of full-sized Gem soldiers.
这边确实好沉寂啊
It does get pretty quiet around here.
来吧，青金石
Come on, Lapis.
咱们把拖拉机拆了吧
Let's go disassemble the tractor.
她们就是想要创造些会动的蔬菜
All they wanted to do is make a living vegetable.
等下!
Wait!
我知道怎么做啊
I know how to do that.
石榴说过不要舔地上捡来的东西
Garnet says not to lick stuff I find on the ground, but,
这次是有正当理由的
this is for a good cause.
♪♪
快点，史蒂文!
Hurry, Steven!
橄榄石，慢着点
Peridot, slow down.
你得看看这个 我们成功了!
But you need to see. We did it!
看来你还是对蔬菜缺乏了解啊
Guess you don't know how vegetables work, after all.
对啊 真是开了眼界呢
Yeah. You guys sure showed me.
来吧，我的小小造物
Come, now, my little creation.
你可以来帮我们收获
You can assist in harvesting
你的同类
the rest of your kind.
啊，应该是因为我兜里装了些
Uh, must be the pumpkin treats
南瓜点心
in my back pocket.
根本说不通啊
That doesn't make sense.
我们创造了它!
We made it!
它应该听我们的才对!
It should listen to us!
它才刚刚诞生出来
It's only just come into existence
就已经不喜欢我们了
and it already doesn't like us.
哦，别这样
Oh, come on.
去找橄榄石和青金石
Go to Peridot and Lapis.
哦
Oop.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我觉得它喜欢我是因为
I think he's coming to me because
其实是我创造了它
I'm the one who made him.
哦
Oh.
这就说得通了
That explains it.
嘛，我们至少种出来了这个
Well, we made this one.
还...还行吧
It's...okay.
但你看看史蒂文那个
But look at Steven's.
有胳膊有腿的
It has a face, and everything.
确实
It's true.
我们这个连张脸都没有
Ours doesn't have a face.
哦不
Oh, no!
别伤心啊
Don't be sad.
在这儿等着，我有个主意!
Wait right here. I have an idea!
我爹以前教过我怎么做这个
My dad showed me how to do this, once.
第一步，先挖个嘴出来
First, we make a mouth.
然后再挖两只
Then we make two
眼
eyes.
嗯，看起来还行
Hmm, lookin' pretty good.
哦，说起来
Oh, you know what?
我差点忘了最重要的一步
I almost forgot a really important step.
得把它挖空
You have to hollow it out.
吔!
Yay!
它现在喜欢我们了
It loves us now.
嗷，没事的南瓜头
Awww, it's okay, Veggie Head.
那个野蛮人抓不到你的
That brute can't get you now.
哦
Oh.
多一个家人也是很不错的
It's nice to have a new addition to the family.
哈?
Huh?
啊--啥?!我了个...?!
Ah -- what?! What the...?!
有流浪汉闯进了谷仓!
Hobos broke into the barn.
嘿!别碰我们的东西!
Hey! Don't you touch our things!
你们是流浪姑娘?
You're hobettes?
流浪汉可是男性的职业
A hobo is a man's job.
那个瞎叫唤的人类是谁啊?
Who's the human and what's he yelling about?
更合理的问题是：
The real question is:
我的战斗无人机呢?
where are my attack drones? [Beeping]
等一下
Wait a minute.
这些神秘的装置
Those mysterious constructions,
你们奇怪的外表
your weird appearance,
还有你奇怪的宝石
your strange jewels.
我知道你们是什么了
I know what you are.
你们是嬉皮士!
You're hippies!
我在收音机里听说过你们
I heard about you on AM radio.
你们为什么要来这儿
What are you doin', comin' in here,
搞坏掉好好的一个传统美国谷仓!
socializin' this fine, American barn?
呃
-Ugh.
哇
Whaaah!
哦，终于来了
Oh, there they are.
等下!不要伤害他!
Wait! Don't hurt him!
但是他在攻击我们和我们的家啊
But he's attacking us, and our home.
呃，你好!
Uh, hello!
近来怎样啊!
How's it goin'?!
呃，你觉着呢?
Uh, how do you think?
呃，这个...
Uh, yeah...
我们就是想知道你想要什么
We just wanted to know what you want.
我想要什么?
What I want?
我想要你们这群嬉皮士滚出我的谷仓!
I want you hippies out of my barn!
你的谷仓?
Your barn?
她们到了
There they are.
格雷格收到了你的短信 我们就跟来了
Greg got your message and we came, too.
那个人类在给你们捣乱是吗?
Is that the human giving you trouble?
我说过你们可以养条看门狗
I told you you two could use a guard dog.
这个也行吧
I guess that works.
你们在对上面这家伙做些什么啊?
What're you doin' to that guy up there?
就...
Just...
放下来他而已
putting him down.
呃!
Uhhh!
没礼貌
Not cool.
格雷格?
Greg?
安迪?
Andy?
他们俩认识?
They know each other?
真巧了
This is perfect!
来，帮我赶走这群吃闲饭的
Come on, help me chase off these freeloaders.
她们对我使了些心灵控制的把戏
They're usin' some kinda hippie mind tricks.
-呃
-Um...
谁告诉你们能
-Who told you
住进来这里然后搞乱我的地盘?
you could move in here and mess this whole place up?
是我，安迪
I did, Andy.
是你?
You did?
这是我父母的谷仓
This is my parents' barn.
嗯，老爸，这位是谁啊?
Um, Dad, who's this?
老爸?
"Dad"?
你是说...?
You mean...?
没门儿
No way.
史蒂文，这位是安迪
Steven, this is Andy.
他是我堂兄
He's my cousin.
安迪，这是史蒂文
Andy, meet Steven.
他是我...
He's my...
儿子
son.
哇!真的很高兴见到你!
Wow! It's really nice to meet you!
所以我该称呼你为堂叔?
Does that mean you're my... first cousin, once removed?
别管这些称呼了
Forget that nonsense.
哦
Oyyy!
你叫我安迪叔叔就好
You call me Uncle Andy.
我当叔叔了 难以置信
I'm an uncle. I can't believe it.
格雷格，你个小犊子
Greg, ya little turd,
你为什么一直没告诉我?
how come you never told me?
我该怎么告诉你啊?!
How was I supposed to?!
我多少年都没见过你了!
I haven't seen you in years!
你以为是谁的错?!
And whose fault is that?
你觉得自己那么优越
You thought you were so much better than us,
然后就自己开车跑掉了
you just got in your van and drove away.
那破事儿都快二十年了!
That was like two decades ago!
安迪叔叔，能放我下来吗
Uncle Andy, can I get down now?
哦，不好意思 史蒂文
Oh, sorry, Steven.
我以前没有抱过侄子
I'm not used to holdin' nephews.
因为我都不知道我还有个侄子!
'Cause I didn't know I had one!
所以，这里面哪位是你媳妇儿啊?
So, uh, which one of these girls is the wife?
我得替她的婚姻默哀三分钟啊，是吧?
I gotta give her my condolences, right?
嘿，别这样，还得我来猜是吗?
Hey, come on. What, I gotta guess, here?
那我猜就是你了
It's gotta be you.
这坨废柴
I bet this useless lump
得有个大女孩儿来管教
needs a big girl to keep him in line.
不是说你胖啊，我意思
You're not big. I'm just sayin'.
只是说你挺高的，你懂
You're tall, not, you know.
玫瑰她
Rose is
已经不在了
no longer with us.
呃，哇
Uh, wow.
我-我很抱歉
I-I'm sorry.
我不知道
I didn't know.
她们算是玫瑰的家人
These people are sort of like her family,
所以我就允许她们俩住在谷仓
so I offered to let these two stay in the barn.
是吗?啊，好吧
Yeah? Ah, well,
那你真是心眼儿善良呢
that was real nice of ya.
但是谷仓是属于五月家的
But the barn's for the DeMayo family.
啥-啥是五月啊?
Wh-What's a DeMayo?
安迪 五月
Andy DeMayo.
格雷格 五月
Greg DeMayo.
史蒂文 五月
Steven DeMayo.
我们是五月家啊
We're the DeMayos.
事实上，我们，嗯
Actually, we're, um,
改名叫宇宙了
the Universes, now.
你个太空大核桃!
You space walnut!
你连自家姓都不要了
You didn't even keep the family name,
却把家里财产随便分给别人
but you're goin' around, givin' family property out like candy
跟什么节日里
on...some kind of
分糖果似的?
candy-givin'-out holiday?
你是在说宇宙
You're telling me Universe
不是个真的姓?!
isn't a real last name?!
是个真的姓
It is a real name.
我已经改过了
I had it changed.
安迪，你瞧，她们真的很需要个地方
Andy, look, they just really needed a place.
她们是外星难民
They're alien refugees from space and --
她们是非法移民?!
They're illegal. aliens?!
这..你甚至都没娶个美国妹子?
Wha...? You couldn't even marry an American?!
那又怎样啊?!
What does that matter?!
五月这个姓比宇宙酷多了
DeMayo's a much cooler name than plain old Universe.
你背弃了自己的家人
You turned your back on your family,
就是为了能跟
just so you could get in with a bunch
一群嬉皮火星移民在一起?
of weirdo, hippie, Martian immigrants?!
你俩，滚出我的星球
You two, get the heck off my planet,
滚出我的国家，滚出我的谷仓!
out of my country, and out of my barn!
唤醒战斗无人机
Reactivating attack drones.
啊，等等!
Ah! Wait!
安迪叔叔?
Uncle Andy?
怎么?
Yeah?
很抱歉我们强占了谷仓
I'm sorry we took over the barn.
我们不知道还有其他家人
I didn't even know we had any other family
能一起分享
to share it with.
你不知道，是吧?
You didn't, huh?
但是这个谷仓
But this barn?
对我们意味着很多
It means a lot to all of us.
我们在这儿共度了很多时光
We spent so much time together here.
这个，我家人也在这儿花了很多时间
Well, my family spent a lot of time here, too.
每年一次，我们会在这里汇合
Once a year, we'd all meet up here,
聊天，吃大餐，找乐子
catch up, eat a big meal, have a good time.
年复一年的家庭传统
Years and years of family tradition.
哦，是吗?
Oh, yeah?
这个我们也能做啊
Well, we can do that, too.
我们这儿有田地，种了很多食物
We've got a farm here, with plenty of food.
我们来做一顿传统大餐，然后一起享用
Let's make a big, traditional meal, and eat it together.
你会度过很愉快的时光
You'll have a good time,
然后你就不得不承认她们是家人
and then, you'll have to admit they're family.
你会把家人踢出谷仓吗?
And would you kick family out of the family barn?
啊...
Ahh...
格雷格
Greg,
你真幸运有个这么可爱的儿子
you're lucky you got such a cute kid.
我知道肯定不是遗传你的
I know he didn't get it from you.
所以，你会让她们...
So, you're letting them...
我给你和这群女巫一次机会
I'll give your coven a chance
吃你们做的大餐
and eat your dinner,
但是仅仅是因为我不小心把三明治
but only 'cause I lost my sandwich
丢在大西洋里了
in the Atlantic.
现在 容我失陪
Now, excuse me.
我得把我的东西拿出飞机
I gotta go get my junk out of the plane.
你觉得这能成吗?
You think this'll work?
也许吧
Maybe.
以安迪他的性格
Andy's never been the type
改变他的主意简直没可能
to change his mind about something,
这次真的是彻底惹恼了他
and he's really got his longjohns in a twist.
让他冷静下来真的要做很多
It's gonna take a lot to calm him down.
我不喜欢这家伙
I don't like this guy.
我不喜欢这个--呃--
I don't like some -- ugh --
新的格雷格突然出现在这儿
new Greg just showin' up outta nowhere.
我们这个格雷格显然好很多
Our Greg is clearly the superior one.
我们才不会离开自己的家
We're not leaving our home.
如果这土块儿以为他能摆弄我们..!
If that clod thinks he can push us around...!
安迪是史蒂文家的一员
Andy is a part of Steven's family.
我们应该努力让他高兴
We should make an effort to get on his good side.
他是我家人，那他也是你们家人
If he's my family, then he's yours, too.
宝石人没有家庭
Gems don't have family.
至少在我们来这里之前如此
At least, not before we came here.
所以，看在家人的份子上，教教我们该做什么
So, for the sake of our family, tell us what to do.
我们来做菜
Let's get cookin'.
好
Okay.
把下一行也拔掉
Gimme the next row.
好
All right.
哇
-Whoa.
你这位阿姨，呃，挺强壮的
Your aunt is, uh, pretty strong.
她有在健身
She works out.
嗯，我猜也是
Yeah, I'll bet.
不好意思，高飞球
Sorry. Fly ball.
棒!
Yeah!
看起来棒极了!
This looks amazing!
虽然是个蔬菜园，还真是“果实”累累呢
For a vegetable garden, I'd say we're pretty fruitful.
晚餐内容就只有一堆蔬菜?
Is it just gonna be a bunch of vegetables?
我早该想到的
I shoulda figured.
你们是群素食主义者!
You're a bunch of vegetarians!
用家族的爱浇灌的蔬菜
A vegetable grown by a family's love
能滋润身体和灵魂的
nurtures the body and soul.
啊，别让他们唬了你，史蒂文
Ah, don't let 'em get to ya, Steven.
我会送你一根大辣肠
I'll getcha a stick o' pepperoni
做生日礼物的
for your birthday.
嗯...
Hmm...
把它调到2000度左右吧
Let's turn it down to around 2,000 degrees,
暂时这样
for now.
听起来好弱鸡
Sounds puny.
我喜欢上面这个螺旋桨
I like the propeller on it.
有点安迪主题的感觉
It's like it's Andy-themed.
我猜他会爱死这个的
I bet he's gonna love this.
蔬菜准备好了吗!
We're ready for the veggies now!
马上来，史嘟宝
Be over in a sec, Stu-ball.
嗯\Mm!
要我说，看起来有点多--
Seems like too much, if ya ask me --
啊，你们都干了些啥?!
Awww, what have you done?!
呃，安迪叔叔?
Uh, Uncle Andy?
伙计，哪儿有问题?
Dude, what's wrong?
我来告诉你哪儿有问题，伙-计
I'll tell you what's wrong, du-u-de.
满哪儿都是问题!
Everything!
你难道看不到面前这个
Can you not see this abomination
机械怪胎吗?!
sittin' right in front of you?!
你在说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
我在说这个引擎，孩子
It's the engine, boy.
这个引擎!
The engine!
她们拆毁了我父母的飞机然后做了这个--
They butchered my parents' plane and made --
这个--管他是什么东西!
made -- whatever this thing is!
这是个烤箱/灶头二合一
It's an oven/ cooktop combo.
糟透了!
It's terrible!
这个可是我们家勇敢五月
That was the heart of the legendary wings
这架传奇飞机的心脏
of the Daring DeMayos.
我就在这架飞机上学的驾驶!
I learned to fly on this plane!
这个垃圾一直都没人用过
No one was even using that junk.
现在至少有点用处了
Now, it's actually good for something.
瞧，这就是你们这类人的问题
See, that's the problem with people like you.
你们觉得所有东西都是自己的
You think everything just belongs to you,
因为你们觉得东西不该有主人
'cause nothing belongs to anybody,
然后就心安理得地据为己有
and you take it and everything's cool.
但是这行为太差了!
And it ain't cool!
安迪?
Andy?
我需要自己静静
I'm gonna need a moment.
我-我现在看不得这个东西
I-I can't look at this right now.
呃--
Uh --
安迪，等下!
Andy, hold up!
她们又不知道!
They didn't know!
好吧，我懂了
Right, I get it:
守法好公民啊
in-laws.
情况水深火热啊
This is going down in flames.
我相信格雷格能解决这件事的
I'm sure Greg will turn this around.
你什么意思，你没有
What do you mean, you weren't
合法结婚?!
technically married?!
你瞧，安迪--
Look, Andy --
我们得升级战略了
We gotta up our game.
这得需要一个终极派对
It's going to take the ultimate party
才能挽回局面
to turn this around.
就像，史上最棒的派对
Like, all the best parties of all time,
加起来一样!
put together!
我想这是可行的
I think that's doable.
等会儿见!
See you in a bit!
玩得开心!
Have fu-u-u-n!
准备好了?
Ready?
南瓜受什么刺激了?
What's got into Pumpkin?
哇!
Whoa!
冷静点，伙计
Chill out, dude.
你确定我帮不上你的忙?
You sure I can't help you with anything?
啊，没关系的
Ah, it's okay.
安迪叔叔和我包办了
Uncle Andy and I got it.
哇，完整的一条!
Whoa! It's one peel!
你黛比阿姨和我都经常会负责做饭
Aunt Deb and I usually got put on kitchen duty
在以前的家族聚会那时候
when the family got together.
那时候我削了超级多土豆
I've peeled a lotta potatoes in my day.
啊，黛比阿姨最近在忙什么啊?
Ah, man, what's Aunt Deb been up to, lately?
你突然又关心起黛比了?
Suddenly, you care about Aunt Deb?
哦，好奇先生
Oh, Mr. Curiosity.
我试试把二十年的情况用一句话说清楚好了
Let's see if I can cram 20 years into a sentence.
我得把这些放到炉子上
Uh, I'm gonna get these on the stove.
行
Sure.
嘿，还真能用啊
Hey, it works.
我想这些飞机零件
You know, I guess it's good
能派上用场还是挺不错的
these plane parts are gettin' some use.
我意思是，回收利用也许没那么糟呢
I mean, maybe recyclin' isn't so bad.
不管怎样，你也有一架新飞机了不是
Looks like you got a new plane, anyway.
她可是个很好的飞机呢
She's a good one, too.
我驾着她飞遍了全球
Been all over the world in that thing.
你全世界都去过?
You've been all over the world?
你最好信我的话
You better believe it.
真的是别有一番体验呢
It's really somethin' else, you know?
只有你，和引擎的轰鸣在稀薄的空气里
Just you and the hum of your engine up in that thin air.
没有别人，没有活物，来，呃
No other people, no livin' things around to, uh,
来陪伴你
keep you company.
但是就算我在地面上
But, you know, it's not like there's much for me
也没有人在我身边了
down on the ground, these days either, so.
呃，安迪叔叔?
Uh, Uncle Andy?
你的阿姨们回来了
Your aunts are back.
安迪，我们听说
So, Andy, we heard
你喜欢婚姻，所以我们想着
you like marriage, so we thought
“为什么不互相嫁给对方呢?”
"Why don't we all marry each other?"
如果你觉得这还不够人类的话
And, if that's not human enough for you,
我们还可以加入一些诞生
we can throw in a little being born
和一点死亡
and some dying.
我们对你的婚姻感到十分遗憾
We're very sorry for your marriage.
我们试着包括人的一生中
We tried to cover as many celebrations
所有的庆典活动
in the human life span as we could.
棒
Nice.
哦，天啊
Oh, boy!
好吧好吧，我认输
Okay, okay, I give up.
简直太搞笑了!
It's too much!
好吧，我该坐在哪儿?
All right. Where am I sitting?
我们现在开吃怎么样啊，你们说?
Whaddya say we get right to it, huh?
这样吧，如果我们不打算
And, hey, if we're throwin' all tradition
坚守传统习惯的话
out the window, anyway,
为什么不先从蛋糕吃起呢?
why don't we start with this gorgeous cake?
饭前吃甜点
Dessert before dinner.
我真是不礼貌
Where are my manners?
史蒂文，传给你的朋友
Steven, pass it to your friend.
哦
Oh.
我真是不礼貌
Where are my manners?
哦
Oh.
我真是不礼貌
Where are my manners?
哦，谢谢你，青金石
Oh! Thank you, Lapis.
我真是不礼貌
But where are my manners?
哦!
Ohhh!
我真是不礼貌!
Where are my manners?
安迪
Andy.
怎么?
What?
你们不喜欢吃蛋糕?
You guys don't like cake?
宝石人不吃东西的
Gems don't really eat.
当然，除了紫晶之外
Well, except for Amethyst.
我已经饱了
I'm good.
我刚刚已经，喝了三瓶烹饪用油
I had like, three bottles of cooking oil earlier.
这真是...
That's uh...
还好
all right.
我就说我们忘了些什么：
That's what we forgot:
色拉油
more cooking oil.
还有那个购物车!
And the shopping cart!
我们该一起拿来的
We should've taken it.
我们本可以把它塞进那卡车旁的墙里的
We could've put it in the wall next to the truck.
那种行为叫做偷窃
That would've been stealing.
应该算是“车辆”盗窃？
'Cause it's made out of steel?
我们不是拯救了地球吗?
Didn't we save the Earth?
我们应该享有地球上的所有东西!
We should have access to everything on it, by right!
至少也得打个折啊
Or at least get a discount.
你们几个觉得自己在拯救地球?
You guys think you're savin' the Earth?
从母星手上救下地球
Saving the Earth from Homeworld
本身就是一种奖励了
is its own reward.
你知道还有什么能作为奖励吗?
You know what else would be a reward?
物质奖励!
A reward!
好吧
All right.
我们不要在餐桌上挑起另一次
We don't want to start another Gem War
宝石战争了
at the table.
哦，别挑起来哟
Ooh, don't start it.
那要是我把这个餐桌
What if I just came to this table
占为殖民地呢，因为我是个母星宝石?
and started colonizing it, 'cause I'm a Homeworld Gem?
但是你不能这么做啊!
But you can't!
这桌子上还有玉米呢
This table has corn on it
多么美好的事物啊!
and it's beautiful
我们会保卫它的!
and we'll defend it!
哦!
-Oh!
你说得对
You're right.
我们现在在桌子旁待了一会儿后
Now that I've spent time at the table,
我也感受到玉米的可贵!
I can see the value of your corn!
为什么不把那玉米塞进镜子里
Why don't you put that corn in a mirror
待上个一千年
for thousands of years
然后再看看它对桌子什么感觉
and then see how it feels about the table.
它会真的
Really
真的恨这个桌子
hate the table!
你造吗，谢谢你史蒂文
You know what? Thank you, Steven.
准备这顿大餐真的是个好主意
Putting this meal together was a great idea.
哦，不，我应该谢谢石榴
Oh, no, I should be thanking Garnet.
她采集了这些蔬菜
She gathered up all the vegetables.
青金石和橄榄石种植了它们
Lapis and Peridot grew them.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦，是珍珠
Oh, but, it was Pearl
驾车带我们去了“商店”
who drove us to the "store."
这个，我得谢谢史蒂文
Well, I have to thank Steven
烹饪了这些蔬菜
for cooking the vegetables
还有谢谢紫晶扑灭了火
and Amethyst, for putting out that grease fire.
还有点起了火
And starting it.
哦，谢谢格雷格借我们他的车
Oh, and, thanks to Greg for lending his van.
可以说我们得感谢所有人
I guess you could say we can thank everyone.
对的
Yes.
所有人都被感谢了吗?
Was everyone thanked?
被感谢的都举起手!
Raise your hand if you were thanked!
嘿，还有安迪呢
Hey, uh, what about Andy?
嗯...
Hmm...
谢谢安迪，
Thank you, Andy, for
的出现!
showing up!
因为你
Because of you,
所有人都来了谷仓--
everyone came out here to the barn and --
我们现在都聚在一起了
and, now, we're all in one place together
这可是很长时间以来第一次
for the first time in a while.
这确实是件很棒的事
And it's actually pretty great.
那么，万岁!
So, cheers!
万岁!
Cheers!
啊
Ah.
都给你们了
You can have it.
这个谷仓 是你们的了
The barn. It's yours.
我们做错了什么吗?
Did we do something wrong?
我还以为我说的话很贴心呢
I thought I said something really sentimental.
不!等等!
No! Wait!
他不能走!
He can't leave!
青金石
Lapis.
嗯
Hmm.
呃
Uhh.
我在想什么?
What was I thinkin'?
嗨，安迪叔叔!
Hi, Uncle Andy!
啊!什么?!
Ah! What?!
你在干嘛啊，孩子?!
What are you doin', kid?!
我以为一切都很好来着
I thought everything was going really well.
有什么不对的地方吗?
Is something wrong?
是啊，有些地方很不对
Yeah, something's wrong.
比如你飞在天上
You're a mile in the sky,
挂在一位飞翔的女孩儿上!
hangin' off a floatin' lady!
回家吧!
Go home!
你为什么要离开?
Why'd you leave?
我是唯一没离开的那个
I'm the only one who didn't.
是你的蠢爹他
It was your goofball father who was
第一个独自离开跑到了这里来
the first one to hightail it outta here.
然后，是你黛比阿姨
Then, after him, it was Aunt Deb.
她和她的伙伴买了房车
She and her partner got the RV.
有了那房车她也没理由留下
No reason to stick around, with that thing.
爷爷搬去了Keystone
Grandpa moved to the Keys.
他太老了开不了车
Too old to make the drive anymore.
我是唯一一个
I was the only one who tried
试着保持生活原样的人
to keep everything how it used to be.
我知道家庭的真正意义
I knew what it meant to really be a family.
那又帮我找回了什么呢，嗯?
And look what that got me, huh?
什么都没!
Nothin'!
啊，不，等等!
Ah! No! Wait!
抓紧
Hold on.
啊啊啊
Aaaaah!
青金石，把我扔到飞机上
Lapis, throw me onto the plane.
好
Okay.
啥?!我发誓
What?! I swear,
如果你敢扔了他，我--
if you throw him, I'll --
我在谷仓那边和你汇合!
I'll meet you back at the barn!
收到
Roger.
哇!
Whoa!
你扰乱了我的平衡!
You're throwin' off my balance!
你会让我俩都掉下去的!
You're gonna bring us both down!
安迪!我很高兴咱俩都喜欢吃蛋糕!
Andy! I love that we both eat cake!
啥?
What?!
还有你那顶酷帽子!
And you have that cool hat!
还有你很会削土豆!
And you know how to peel potatoes.
还有你要开飞机才能飞
And you need a plane to fly.
我爱那些宝石人，但是
I love the Gems, but,
我也是个人类
I'm a human, too.
我从来没有机会去了解
I never had a chance to know that part
我的人类家人，但是现在我了解了
of my family, but, now, I do.
安迪，我想做你的家人
Andy, I want to be your family.
这不就是你回来的理由?
Isn't that why you came back?
啊!
Ahhh!
啊!史蒂文，你抓紧了!
Aah! Steven, you better hold on!
呃
Unh!
啊
Ah!
史蒂文!
Steven!
悬浮，悬浮，悬浮!
Float, float, float!
苹果派，电子游戏
Apple pie, videogames,
刚洗好的衣物
fresh laundry.
安迪!
Andy!
刚才真险呢，安迪叔叔
That was a close one, Uncle Andy.
你确实很会--
You sure are good at --
你有想过你会怎样吗?!
Do you have any idea what coulda happened to you?!
做家人又有什么用呢，如果你死...
What good are you to me as family if you're...?
对不起
Sorry.
我只是--
Look, I just -- ah,
我很高兴你安全了
I'm just glad that you're safe.
感觉太不公平了
It just doesn't feel fair.
所有事都变得那么陌生
Everything got so different.
我希望所有人都能保持原样，但是他们--
I wanted everybody to stay the same, but they --
他们都在变
they just didn't.
天啊，我究竟在做些什么?
Jeez, what am I even doin'?
我有架飞机
I got an airplane.
我能拜访所有人!
I could've been visitin' everybody,
不论他们去了哪
everywhere they went.
我也早该知道你的存在
I could've known about you.
我想我也早该做些改变
I guess I could've just changed, too, you know.
现在还不晚
It's not too late.
我们会在你身边的
We're here.
如果你想的话
If you want us to be.
不!
No!
说“土块儿”
Say "clod."
特五块儿
Cuh-lah-duh.
史蒂文!
Steven!
嗨!
Hi-i!
安迪，再见到你真好
Andy, it's good to see you again.
我很抱歉我--
I'm sorry if --
嘿
Hey, uh,
你们应该还有些剩菜剩饭吧?
you guys probably got a lotta leftovers, right?
我就想着回来帮你们解决掉
I-I just figured I'd come back and help you with that.
你造的，你们不是不吃东西嘛
You know, since you don't eat, and all.
是的，当然了
Yes, of course.
我们会帮你准备好的
We'll get everything in order.
谢谢你的谷仓!
Well, thanks for the barn!
嘿，安迪?
Hey, Andy?
我很高兴你回来了
I'm really glad you came back.
啊，到这儿来，你个蠢蛋
Ah, c'mere, you goofball.
你该剪头了，孩子
You need a haircut, son.
南瓜!
-Pumpkin!
嘿，如果你有剩下点什么的的话
Hey, you got some leftovers for me, too,
你个小
you little --
你个小怪物
you little freak o' nature, there?
这真是，呃
That's, uh...
真是恶心呢
That's gross.
♪♪